Now I will test that extension, this is how it looks like.
First I will probably go, I want to reorder it alphabetically and I want to have it everything
collapsed by default and divide some categories to social media and discovery in the
general.
First I will destroy, so I am on a blue sky app.
If I go here and try this blue sky, I can try profile extract.
It is executed and we have easily, that is great.
Obviously we can copy this id and if I go to any post like this, that is not related to the
user and the second close because this is JavaScript code, I will go again to a blue sky
open profile by id, we will open it up, press ID, it will directly open his account.
Alright, so I want to just add the quick changes, so the first I will just add new features
as a new agent, I want you to add a catalog called social media, and put social media
book marklets, inside and sort them out vertically, okay, so run this agent and I will open
a new agent and this agent will work on a new feature, I want you to add a feature that
will allow the user to add a star and maybe not a star to add the pin, favorite book
marklet category that will appear here will pin one or more and it should be on
the right side of that book marklet entry, so I will open a new one, we can see another
one that is awaiting review, so as you can see it has updated and because I am running
another task that is in the meantime, I want it to update but soon I am going to show
you how you can actually use, so just open it up and obviously I will use this as a half
a day, the awesome book mark, the own scenes, okay, is done, I press your fresh, I don't
see any error, that's great, so I'll open this guy again, open a two amount account and
open here and that's great, so we can pin a category but I don't want to pin category,
I want just to probably pin only the entry, so it's like a file and that's I like, so
we've set in the general and social media, okay, so first I want this one, I want you
to collapse all of the categories by default and remove over with the background, because
we get the default one, what I mean by that because if you go to book marklet and open
up here, we see that even if you hover, you can list all the links in this place like a natural
and this video and then pin feature and don't want to pin categories but entries and category
both in it, entries should appear at the top when we add at least one entry, book marklet
and after it's added in this category, there should be an outcome, but we can remove it
from the favorites, it's switching to pin in the robot market entries and I'm letting
the code, we see it run out here, okay, all right, so we see both of this task were completed,
and now we'll go back to the Chrome extension itself, manage extension and our refresh
and opening that, nice, nice, like, very cool, so you have a links discovery and social media
and we can pin anything, so I want to pin, for example, blue sky and profile extract
and press pin and unfortunately I have a possibility to add, but it's still not visible
if I have a social media because if I have full files, I see the bottom but it doesn't
add like a new category, so even if I open it up now, it doesn't, but it saves the status,
it won't open and open, okay, so we see two issues, it's great, but when I reopen a
Chrome popup after it makes first category not collapsed and the pin feature, I see a pin
feature but when I press it, it doesn't add a category, favorites, add it up to easy, use
it, please add a favorite category, that is empty and when we press a pin, copy that
entry to those category and allow it to remove, okay, so as you can see, this is the
editing social media, fixed issue, Chrome was restoring the previous state, so automatic
way of re-open, so yeah, because it's obviously running, and now we can add a new pin
option, as we can see, it's replacing the render function, I don't think the favorite
is category, okay, we see updated features, now go again to the Chrome extension, now
just update here and when I go, I see favorites, oh, actually it's now signing, it changes
the visibility that I wanted, that's pretty great, so now even the profile extract, I'll
go to an extension, open it up, everything is used and I'll just press one and as you
can see it's now greatly worked, so just click profile extract, I think it's a very great
and I like the design, and we can play in it, like reverse voice, and I will just create
a new own scripts, I will show how we can create manual scripts, how we can create
scripts by using a chat deputy and cloud stack key, so we will just populate this area,
subcategory area, the new custom ones, make a nice library and then add this Chrome extension
to the Chrome Web Store.